Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Records SC0112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Libraries, records
circa 1891-2017
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Weber, David C.
Stanford University. Libraries
SC0112
493.75 Linear Feet
Related Collections
SC0756
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Libraries, University and college.; Collection development (Libraries); Academic libraries; Academic libraries -- California.; Weber, David C.; Stanford University. Libraries
- Early library records, Series 1A
- Early Director's Files, Series 1B
  - General correspondence, 1942 (Box 124)
  - General correspondence, 1942 (Box 125)
  - General correspondence, 1943 (Box 126)
  - General correspondence, 1943 (Box 127)
  - General correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 128)
  - General correspondence, 1944 (Box 129)
  - General correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 130)
  - General correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 131)
  - General correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 132)
  - General correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 133)
  - General correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 134)
  - General correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 135)
  - General correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 136)
- Director's Office, Series 2
  - Collection Development: Elmer M. Grieder papers, 1967-1974
    - Abel, Richard, & Co. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Acession Lists (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Acquisition Inquiries (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Acquisition-Order Division (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Africa (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Afro-American Collection (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Anthropolgy and Education Biblography (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Approval Agreements (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Art Library (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Audio Visual (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Bernstein, A. (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Book Funds (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Branch Libraries (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - British Publishers--Archives (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - CAE Bibliography (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Catalog Department (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Catholic Microfilm Center (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Research (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Chicano Library (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Circulation, Storage, and Transfer (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Classics (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Data Files and Services (Including Committee) (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Director's Conference (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Dissertation (Foreign) (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Documents (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - East Asia/Souteast Asia (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - English Department (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - ERIC/Stanford (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Exchanges (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Relations (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Statements (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Financial Campaign (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Germanic Languages (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Gifts (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - History Department (Box 89, Folder 35)
    - Honorary Curators (Box 89, Folder 36)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 89, Folder 37)
    - Hopkins Transportation Library (Box 89, Folder 38)
    - Human Biology (Box 89, Folder 39)
    - Icelandic (Box 89, Folder 40)
    - Interlibrary Loan (Box 89, Folder 41)
    - International Studies (Box 89, Folder 42)
    - James, William (Box 89)
    - Japanese (Box 89, Folder 43)
    - Late-in-Year Proposals (Box 89, Folder 44)
    - Latin America (Box 89, Folder 45)
    - Law Library (Box 89, Folder 46)
    - LC Proof Slips (Box 89, Folder 47)
    - Lethcoe, N. (Box 89, Folder 48)
    - Librarianship, Committee on (Box 89, Folder 49)
    - Library Instructions (Box 89, Folder 50)
    - Library Publications (Box 89, Folder 51)
    - Maps (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Meyer Undergraduate Library (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Microfilm Projects (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Music Library (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - New Left (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Newspapers (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Overseas Campuses (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Paret Military (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Personnel-Inca Rumold (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Philosophy (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Publisher's Weekly-British National Bibliography (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Reference (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Rejects (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Religious Studies (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Reprints (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Romance Languages (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Russian and East European (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Russian and East European (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Santa Clara County Information Net. (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Science Division (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Serials (Including Union Lists) (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Special Collections (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Staff Classifications, Status, etc. (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Stanford University Librarians Association (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Stencils (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Subject and Language Advisors-Library and Faculty (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Subscription Cancellation Project (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Unions (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Urban Studies Planning (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Visiting Committee (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Women's Studies (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Working Papers (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Files of the Assistant Director for Business Services
    - Budget Administration, 1963-64 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1962-63 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1961-62 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1960-61 (Box 94)
    - Permanent Book Funds (Box 94)
    - Book Fund Date (Box 94)
    - Departmental Book Fund Requests, 1957-78 (Box 94)
    - Deparmental Serial Costs (Box 94)
    - Library Development Fund--Closed (Box 94)
    - Book Fund, 1963-66 (Box 94)
    - Book Funds, 1963-64 (Box 94)
    - Book Funds, 1960-61 (Box 94)
    - Book Fund Memorial Fund, 1959-60 (Box 94)
    - Book Fund Memorial Fund, 1958-59 (Box 94)
    - Book Funds, 1962-63 (Box 94)
    - Book Funds, 1958-59 (Box 94)
    - Book Fund Statements, 1962-63 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1966-67 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1965-66 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1965-66 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1964-65 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1967-68 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1969-70 (Box 94)
    - Budget Administration, 1968-69 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1963-64 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1962-63 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1964-65 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1961-62 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1960-61 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1959-60 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1958-59 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1957-58 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1956-57 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1966-67 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1964-65 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget (received 2 Files for this), 1965-66 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1967-68 (Box 94)
    - Official Budget, 1968-69 (Box 94)
  - Public Services: Dale B. Canelas papers
    - General Reference Department
      - General, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - General, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - Budget and Staff, 1976-1979 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - Center Map Collection, 1976-1979 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Current Periodicals and Microtext Div., 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - Current Periodicals and Microtext, 1978-1979 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      - Current Periodicals and Microtext., Budget and Staff, 1976-1978 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - Data Services, 1976-1979 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      - Data Services, Budget and Staff, 1976-1978 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      - Fastbook, 1977-1978 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      - Interlibrary Services, 1976-1978 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      - Interlibrary Services, Budget and Staff, 1976-1978 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      - ILS, Charging (Box 117, Folder 14)
      - ILS, Statistics (Box 117, Folder 15)
      - Technical Information Services, 1976-1980 (Box 117, Folder 16)
      - Reference Manual, 1977-1979 (Box 117, Folder 17)
      - Staff Time Study (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Art Library
      - Art Library, 1977-1978 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Cubberley
      - Education/Cubberley, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Music Library
      - Music Library, 1976-1978 (Box 117, Folder 21)
      - Music Library, Archive of Recorded Sound, Cataloing Project, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Meyer Library
      - Meyer Library, Council, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Science Department
      - Engineering Library, 1976-1978 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Circulation
      - Central Circulation Department, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Central Circulation Department, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Central Circulation Department, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Central Circulation Department, 1976-1980 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Automation (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Binding (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Borrow Categories (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Borrow Information (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Borrowing Regulation, 1969-1978 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Building Access (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - Budget and Staff (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - Cooperative Program Statistics (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - Deployment (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - Fees (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - Graduate Reserves (Box 118, Folder 15)
      - ID Cards (Box 118, Folder 16)
      - Loan (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - Location (Box 118, Folder 18)
      - Locked Stack Project (Box 118, Folder 19)
      - Meyer Basement Flood (Box 118, Folder 20)
      - Patron Problems (Box 118, Folder 21)
      - Physical Facilities and Equipment, 1976-1978 (Box 118, Folder 22)
      - Privileges, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 23)
      - Privileges, Alumni (Box 118, Folder 24)
      - Privileges, Doctoral, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 25)
      - Privileges, Faculty (Box 118, Folder 26)
      - Privileges, Fellows (Box 118, Folder 27)
      - Privileges, Institutions (Box 118, Folder 28)
      - Privileges, Non-Stanford Users (Box 118, Folder 29)
      - Privileges, Proxy (Box 118, Folder 30)
      - Privileges, Retired (Box 118, Folder 31)
      - Privileges, Staff (Box 118, Folder 32)
      - Privileges, United Campus Ministry (Box 118, Folder 33)
      - Privileges, Privileges Desk (Box 118, Folder 34)
      - Speed Processing, 1976-1978 (Box 118, Folder 35)
      - Stack Access, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 36)
      - Stacks, 1976-1979 (Box 118, Folder 37)
      - Storage Facility, 1975-1978 (Box 118, Folder 38)
      - Transfer of Materials, 1974-1978 (Box 118, Folder 39)
    - Government Documents
      - General, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 40)
      - General, 1978-1980 (Box 118, Folder 41)
      - Budget and Staff, 1977-1979 (Box 118, Folder 42)
      - Physical Facilities (Box 118, Folder 43)
      - Technical Processing (Box 118, Folder 44)
      - Terminals (Box 118, Folder 45)
    - Art Library
      - Art Library, General, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Art Library, Budget and Staff, 1977-1980 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Cubberley
      - Cubberley Library, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - Cubberley Library, Budget and Staff, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - Cubberley Library, Reference Services (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Music Library
      - Archive of Recorded Sound (ARS), 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - ARS, Cataloging Projcct, 1976-1977 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - ARS, HP Proposal, 1978-1980 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - ARS, Victor Project, 1977-1980 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Budget And Staff, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - Physical Facilities, 1977-1980 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - Renovation, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Meyer Library
      - General, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - Audio/Visual, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 14)
      - Bibliographic Inst., 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 15)
      - Book Loss, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 16)
      - Budget, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 17)
      - Catalog, 1978-1980 (Box 121, Folder 18)
      - Collection Development, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 19)
      - Council, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 20)
      - Disruptions, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 21)
      - Heating, Ventilation and Air Conditioning, 1977-1980 (Box 121, Folder 22)
      - Hours, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 23)
      - Librarians, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 24)
      - Mission Statement, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 25)
      - Noise Making, 1975-1980 (Box 121, Folder 26)
      - Physical Facilities, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 27)
      - Reserves, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 28)
      - Responses to Patrons, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 29)
      - Security, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 30)
      - Special Projects, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 31)
      - Staff, 1975-1980 (Box 121, Folder 32)
      - Statistics, 1976-1980 (Box 121, Folder 33)
      - Student Lounge, 1976-1978 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Student Monitors (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Supervisors Group (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Surveys, 1974-1978 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Technical Services, 1975-1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Terminals and Terminal Training (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Science Department
      - General, 1975-1978 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Budget, 1977-1980 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Public Service Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Biology Library (Falconer), 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Biology Library (Falconer), Budget and Staff (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - Biology Library (Falconer), Physical Facilities (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - Chemistry Library (Swain), 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - Chemistry Library (Swain), Budget and Staff (Box 122, Folder 14)
      - Chemistry Library (Swain), Physical Faciltiies (Box 122, Folder 15)
      - Earth Sciences Library (Branner), 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 16)
      - Earth Sciences Library (Branner), Physical Facilities (Box 122, Folder 17)
      - Engineering Library, Budget and Staff (Box 122, Folder 18)
      - Hopkins Marine Station, 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 19)
      - Hopkins Marine Station, Physical Facilities (Box 122, Folder 20)
      - Math/Comp. Science Library, 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 21)
      - Math/Comp. Science Library, Physical Facilities (Box 122, Folder 22)
      - Physics Library, 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Working Branch Libraries
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1980 (Box 122, Folder 24)
      - Classics Library (Box 122, Folder 25)
      - Mendenhall Comunications Library (Box 122, Folder 26)
      - Psychology Library (Box 122, Folder 27)
      - Tanner Philosophy Library (Box 122, Folder 28)
      - V.J. West Political Science Library (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Public Service
      - Asilomar (Box 122, Folder 30)
      - Bibiographic Information, 1978-1980 (Box 122, Folder 31)
      - Branch Library Committees, 1971-1980 (Box 122, Folder 32)
      - Coordinating Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 122, Folder 33)
      - Discharged Committees (Box 122, Folder 34)
      - Goals and Objectives (Box 122, Folder 35)
      - Green "Move" Committee (Box 122, Folder 36)
      - Gutenberg Express (Box 122, Folder 37)
      - Hours (Box 122, Folder 38)
      - Information Services, General (Box 122, Folder 39)
      - Interlibrary Services Program (Box 122, Folder 40)
      - Microfiche (Box 122, Folder 41)
      - Physical Facilities (Green) (Box 122, Folder 42)
      - Physically Disabled (Box 122, Folder 43)
      - Physically Limited, Committee on the Disabled, 1978-1979 (Box 122, Folder 44)
      - Portal Monitors, 1979- (Box 122, Folder 45)
      - Responses to Patrons (Box 122, Folder 46)
      - Security (Box 122, Folder 47)
      - Seminar, Laboratory and Office Collections (SLOS) (Box 122, Folder 48)
      - Staff Development (Box 122, Folder 49)
      - Subject Reading Areas (Box 122, Folder 50)
      - Visitors' Brochure (Box 122, Folder 51)
      - Visiting Scholars Rooms (Box 122, Folder 52)
    - Public Services--Equipment (Card Catalog Requests), 1979 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Planning Office Report University Statistics, 1966-76 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Academic Planning Office Report for 1976-77 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Academic Planning Office Report for 1977-78 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Academic Planning Office Report for 1978-79 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - PS--Green--Graphics, 1977/82 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - PS--Move Progress (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - PS--Online Catalog, 1982 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - PS--Online Catalog, 1981 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - PS--Online Catalog, 1979/80 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - PS--Online Catalog Duplicates (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - PS--Responses to Patrons, 1975/80 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Socrates Documentation (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Annual Statistics (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Annual Statistics Miscellaneous (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Annual Statistics Masters and Examples (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Annual Statistics Forms 1-9, 1979/80 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Annual Statistics Forms 1-9, 1978/79 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Annual Statistics Forms 1-9, 1980/81 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Statistics, 1978/79 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Statistics, Form, a, b, c, 1979/80 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Quarterly Statistics Forms (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Statistics, Quarterly, b, c, totals, 1981/82 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Statistics, Quarterly, Miscellaneous (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Statistics, Proposed Changes (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Suggestions, Completed, 1983 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Suggestions, 1980/81 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Suggestions, Completed, 1981/82 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Suggestion box, 1976/80 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - PS--Berkeley--SU, Research Library Coop. Program, 1976/79 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Automation General File, 6/79-6/82 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Automation--CIT, 5/80-7/82 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Automation--RLIN, 9/79-7/82 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Bibliographic Instruction, 5/77-2/82 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Information Resources at Stanford (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Budget Group, 1982 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Committees--Associates (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Committees--Branch Group (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Cable TV Committee (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Committees--Directors Group (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Foreign Students (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Green Group (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Committees--LPPS TF4 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - PSG (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - PSG Minutes (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Committee--PSAG (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Public Services Council, 1980 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Public Services Council, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Public Services Council, 1978-79 (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Public Services Council, 1978 (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Public Services Council, 1977 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Public Services Council, 1976 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Committees--PSCC (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - PS--PSCC, 1976-1979 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Publications (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Committees--RLG--PSC (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - PS--PLG-PSC, Research Libraries Group Public Services Committee--General (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Committees--SULA (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Committees--Visiting Committee (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - PS--Committee Reports--Impact of East Wing (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Discharge Committee--Comm on Reserves (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - PS--Equipment (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - PS--Equipment (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - PS--Graphics, 1977-82 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Graphics (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Guide (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Automated Circulation (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - CIT Accounts (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Course Reserves (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Cooperative Programs: Agreements (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Cooperative Programs: Publicity (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Cooperative Programs: Statistics (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Copyright Guidelines (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Cn. Psa (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Daily Insert:, 1979-80 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Daily Insert:, 1982-83 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Daily Insert: aricle for current year. (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Directors' Office (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Exhibits:, 1977 (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Exhibits:, 1978 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Exhibits:, 1979 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Exhibits:, 1980 (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Format for Biblographies (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Study Terminals (Box 202, Folder 19)
    - Graphics:, 1979-80 (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - Goldbach, Dianne: Chron File (Box 202, Folder 21)
    - Language Abilities (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - Library Tours:, 1980 (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - Literature Searching: Closing Card Catalog (Box 202, Folder 24)
    - Literature Searching: OCLC versus RLIN (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - PSCC (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - PSG Minutes (Box 202, Folder 27)
    - Public Services Committee on Terminals (Box 202, Folder 28)
    - Publications: Hours of Operations--, 1980-81 (Box 202, Folder 29)
    - Public Services Typist (Box 202, Folder 30)
    - Reference Survey (Box 202, Folder 31)
    - RLIN (Box 202, Folder 32)
    - RLIN Collection Development Accounts (Box 202, Folder 33)
    - RLIN Search Only CPU Seconds (Box 202, Folder 34)
    - RLIN Terminal Allocation (Box 202, Folder 35)
    - Room Numbers: Green Library (Box 202, Folder 36)
    - Room 175A Proposal (Box 202, Folder 37)
    - SUL Survey (Box 202, Folder 38)
    - Terminals for Typing Room (Box 202, Folder 39)
    - University of Washington (Box 202, Folder 40)
    - Working Branches (Box 202, Folder 41)
    - Wordstar (Box 202, Folder 42)
    - WYLBUR (Box 202, Folder 43)
    - Interlibrary Services (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Insert Subject Guide/Collections (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Night Parking (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Northern Regional Library Facility (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Office of Post Secondary Education (Grant Proposal) (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Physically Limited (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Staff: Language Abilities (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Library Publications Committee (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Library Publications Committee: Drafts of Guides (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Cabinet--, 1980--82 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Cabinet--, 1982 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - ACCL--, 1975-79 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - ACCL--, 1980 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - ACCL--, 1980-82 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - ULC--, 1982 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - ULC--, 1983 (Box 203, Folder 16)
  - Directors' Office records, 1965-1993; Accession ARCH-2011-171
    - Academic staff classification, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1976-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative action steering committee, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Afro-American Collection, 1968-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Audio Library plans and memos, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Book Selection, 1966-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Annual Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Annual Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Annual Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Annual Budget, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Campaign, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Centennial Planning--sub committee on Undergraduate Research and Honors Programs, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chicano Studies, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Committee Use and Communications, report, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Publications, final report, 1979 Jun (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Copyright revision: library guidelines, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Copyright taskgroup, charge and makeup, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Copyright taskgroup, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Ethnic collections, Meyer, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)